Guide to the Silverstein San Francisco Opera Collection ARS.0071
Archive of Recorded Sound
Silverstein San Francisco Opera Collection
1973-1975
ARS.0071
Silverstein, Lois
1 box: 13 open reel tapes
Archive of Recorded Sound
Off-air recordings of opera performances, mostly from the San Francisco Opera, from 1973 to 1975.
Access
Open for research; material must be requested at least two business days in advance of intended use. Contact the Archive for assistance.
Source
The Silverstein San Francisco Opera Collection was donated to the Stanford Archive of Recorded Sound by Lois Silverstein in July 1993.
Scope and Contents
Thirteen tapes of opera performances, produced almost entirely by the San Francisco Opera, recorded from radio broadcasts from 1973 to 1975.
Indexing Terms
San Francisco Opera.; Operas; San Francisco Bay Area (Calif.)
- Merola Anniversary Concert, Golden Gate Park. Adler, SF Opera Orchestra, Pavarotti, L. Albanese, 1973-09-02; 1; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
- La Favorita. Cillario, SF Opera, Pavarotti (1973-09-07). Two tapes. Side 2 of Tape 2 is Norma conducted by Levine with Sills and Verrett (incomplete, 1974), 1973-1974; 2; 2 7" open reel tapes (Audio 1)
- Manon Lescaut. R. Giovaninetti, SF Opera, L. Price (includes interview with Price), 1974-09-13; 3; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
- Salome. Ohmar Suitner, SF Opera, Rysanek -- Parsifal. Solti, Vienna Philharmonic, Vienna State Opera Chorus (undated), 1974-10-04; 4; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
- Luisa Miller. SF Opera, Pavarotti (KKHI, interview with Pavarotti and Adler) -- Madame Butterfly. Von Karajan, Vienna Philharmonic, Pavarotti (undated), 1974-11-29; 5; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
- Gigli concert, KPFA (1975-08-03) -- Il Tabarro. Shapirra, SF Opera (1975-11-28) -- Gianni Schicchi. Shapirra, SF Opera (1975-11-28), 6; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
- L'Incoronazione di Poppea. R. Leopard, SF Opera, 1975-09-19; 7; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
- Der Friegende Hollander. Schermerhorn, SF Opera, Theo Adam, 1975-09-26; 8; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
- Il Trovatore. Bonynge, SF Opera, Pavarotti, Sutherland, 1975-10-05; 9; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
- Pique Dame. M. Rostropovich, SF Opera, 1975-10-24; 10; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
- Norma. SF Opera -- Anna Bolena (incomplete, undated), 1975-10-31; 11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
- Simon Boccanegra. Paolo Peloso, SF Opera, Kiri Te Kanawa, 1975-11-14; 12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)